{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Health & Psychology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20term%20for%20the%20feeling%20of%20overwhelming%20sadness%20and%20hopelessness%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Depression",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Euphoria",
        "Excitement",
        "Contentment"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Health & Psychology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20activity%20is%20often%20recommended%20as%20a%20way%20to%20improve%20mental%20well-being%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Exercise",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Isolation",
        "Sedentary%20behavior",
        "Excessive%20screen%20time"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Health & Psychology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20a%20common%20way%20to%20manage%20stress%20and%20anxiety%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Deep%20breathing%20exercises",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ignoring%20the%20problem",
        "Increased%20caffeine%20intake",
        "Ruminating%20on%20issues"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Health & Psychology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20is%20a%20common%20symptom%20of%20stress%20overload%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Fatigue",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Heightened%20energy%20levels",
        "Improved%20focus%20and%20clarity",
        "Enhanced%20sleep%20patterns"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Health & Psychology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20an%20important%20factor%20for%20maintaining%20good%20mental%20health%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Quality%20sleep",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Excessive%20alcohol%20consumption",
        "Irregular%20meal%20times",
        "Lack%20of%20physical%20activity"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Health & Psychology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20activity%20can%20help%20in%20reducing%20feelings%20of%20stress%20and%20anxiety%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Meditation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Overthinking",
        "Skipping%20meals",
        "Increased%20caffeine%20intake"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Health & Psychology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20can%20be%20a%20sign%20of%20mental%20well-being%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Positive%20relationships",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Isolation",
        "Constant%20worrying",
        "Pessimistic%20outlook"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Health & Psychology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20activity%20is%20often%20recommended%20to%20boost%20mood%20and%20self-esteem%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Engaging%20in%20hobbies",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Excessive%20screen%20time",
        "Avoiding%20social%20interactions",
        "Skipping%20meals"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Health & Psychology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20can%20aid%20in%20stress%20reduction%20and%20mental%20clarity%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Practicing%20mindfulness",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Multi-tasking",
        "Ruminating%20on%20problems",
        "Increased%20caffeine%20intake"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Health & Psychology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20a%20common%20way%20to%20promote%20positive%20mental%20health%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Expressing%20gratitude",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Focusing%20solely%20on%20work",
        "Ignoring%20emotional%20needs",
        "Isolating%20from%20others"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
